<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>moe.launcher.anime-games-launcher</id>
  <name>Anime Games Launcher</name>
  <summary>Play your favorite anime games on Linux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Spielen Sie Ihre Lieblings-Anime-Spiele auf Linux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Играйте в вашу любимую аниме-игру на линуксе</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juega a tu juego favorito de anime en Linux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gioca al tuo gioco anime preferito su Linux</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Játssz a kedvenc játékoddal Linux-on!</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Anime Games Launcher is an unofficial launcher for a certain video game that handles setting up Wine, installing the game, and patching it to work on Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="de">
    <p>Anime Games Launcher ist ein inoffizieller Launcher für ein bestimmtes Videospiel, welcher die Einrichtung von Wine, die Installation des Spiels und das Patchen, dass es unter Linux läuft, übernimmt.</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="ru">
    <p>Anime Games Launcher - это неофициальный лаунчер для определённой видео-игры, который настраивает Wine, устанавливает игру и применяет дополнительные патчи для предоставления возможности её работы на линуксе.</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="es">
    <p>Launcher de un Juego de Anime es un launcher no oficial para cierto videojuego. Se encarga de configurar Wine, instalar el juego, y parchearlo para que funcione en Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="it">
    <p>Anime Games Launcher è un launcher non ufficiale per un certo videogioco anime che gestisce e configura automaticamente Wine, l'installazione e patching del gioco per farlo funzionare su Linux.</p>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="hu">Az Anime Game Launcher egy nem-hivatalos launcher egy bizonyos videójátékhoz amely helyetted beállítja a Wine-t, telepíti a játékot, és alkalmazza a Linux patch-et hozzá.</description>
  <developer_name>An Anime Team</developer_name>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/an-anime-team/anime-games-launcher/master/repository/main-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/an-anime-team/anime-games-launcher/master/repository/details-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">moe.launcher.anime-games-launcher.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/an-anime-team/anime-games-launcher</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/an-anime-team/anime-games-launcher/issues</url>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <categories>
    <category>Game</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">moderate</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2024-01-12">
      <description>
        <p>Throughout the time I've been working on this project, I've often been asked about creating some sort of "multilauncher" to run all the games instead of using different launchers for different games. As time went on, the number of games our team was supporting grew, and with it the workload on me grew.</p>
        <p>After a lot of work, I'm glad to present you a new project - Anime Games Launcher (and what other name did you expect). It is supposed to be an "anime steam", where you will be able to download the games you need and run them from your "library". The games themselves are added in the format of lua scripts, so the community can actively work on integrating games into the launcher.</p>
        <p>All work on the project was done during my winter vacation (I didn't even have time to rest). Unfortunately, my free time is coming to an end, so I have to do the release earlier than I would like. A lot of things were either not done or done "hastily" for the sake of a quick release. I already have a pretty extensive plan for changes to the launcher, which I will gradually implement in my free time.</p>
        <p>Right now I expect active testing and feedback from users. Although the program has been tested by active participants of our discord server - still expect possible work bugs.</p>
        <p>Thank you very much for your attention.</p>
        <p>With love, An Anime Team.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>contact at kaifa dot ch</update_contact>
</component>
